Rahul S. Chauhan

Raipur, Chhattisgarh, India



rahulschauhan50@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/rahul-s-chauhan-005223199

Summary

JavaScript developer with Native android development skills and have worked on several projects.

Passionate about learning new concepts and frameworks. Open to new and exciting opportunities, challenges and loves to code and debug. Have the ability to handle work pressure and deliver results on time.

I Have skills including C++/C, Python, JavaScript, Java, React Native, React, Node, and Technical Content Writing.

I actively do competitive programming and have a good grasp of Data Structure and algorithms.

Experience

⇒ Intern (Technical Content Writer)

GeeksforGeeks

Aug 2021 - Present (3 months +)

React Native Developer

3 Comma Capital

Jun 2021 - Present (5 months +)

Working as a junior React Native developer.

My day-to-day responsibilities include,

- -Designing beautiful UI Components.
- -Integrating backend API with the app.
- -Writing good quality JavaScript code.
- -Debugging issues in the app.

Education



Government Engineering College Raipur

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Software Engineering 2018 - 2022



Dronacharya Public School

11-12th, PCM 2016 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



JavaScript - HackerRank

521ee42c1fed

- Scientific Computing with Python freeCodeCamp
 - fcca098ad32-8832-4529-905e-ef926e6089b8
- Python HackerRank b1a41906102e
- Java HackerRank 367434a84dd3
- **The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing** Google M27 3QF RWB
- SIH 2020 Finalist Smart India Hackathon 2020

Skills

JavaScript • React.js • Android Development • Algorithms • C++ • Software Development • Web Applications • Java • Python (Programming Language) • React Native